ANDITO

Makassar, South Sulawesi | andito763@gmail.com | 085298973249 | linkedin.com/in/andito28 | github.com/andito28

SHORT DESCRIPTION

I am a Web Developer with 2 years work experience. experienced in collecting, changing and organizing data for analysis and decision making, experienced in developing websites for brands from several industries, such as media and internal company applications. Successfully developing the PT Liny Jaya Informatika attendance application which is used by all employees to carry out attendance and report their respective work, it has been proven that this application can make it easier for employees to evaluate their performance in their work.

SKILL SET

- PHP
- Golang
- Javascript
- Laravel
- Node is
- Iquery
- CSS
- Bootstrap

- API
- CodeIgniter
- SQL
- GIT
- Database Design
- Testing
- JWT
- Passport

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Web Programmer PT. Liny Jaya Informatika

November, 2021 – December, 2022

- Create a responsive and functional interface to enable users to have a good user experience when accessing the website from any device.
- Design and develop user-friendly websites or applications according to client requirements.
- Develop and carry out maintenance of the company's internal systems.

Backend Developer Cv. Alto Perkasa

Januari, 2023 - Current

- Presentation Product to Client;
- Design and develop user-friendly websites or applications according to client requirements.
- Work closely with programmers and other stakeholders to design websites or mobile applications and implement features as per client requests.
- Develop applications using the PHP programming language with the Laravel framework.

INTERNSHIP

Web Developer Lokpro Media

Juni, 2021 - September, 2021

- Develop a website using the Laravel Framework with the team.
- Troubleshot and debugged code ensuring compatibility with devices, browsers and operating systems.
- Shadowed developers to learn key details about job duties and tasks.

FREELANCE PROJECT

- E-Layanan DISDUKCAPIL Kota Makassar(Link Project).
- Website & PPDB SMP-SMA Ittihad Makassar (<u>Link Project</u>).
- Website Komite Olahraga Nasional Indonesia (KONI) Sulsel (<u>Link Project</u>).

COURSE PROJECT

Server Staycation (<u>Github</u>) Back End

September, 2021

- Design system flow for Server Staycation application;
- Design ERD for Server Staycation;
- Create RestFull API Server Staycation using Express JS (Node JS);

Crouwdfunding (Github)

Back End October, 2022

- Design system flow for Crowdfunding application;
- Design ERD for Crouwdfunding;
- Create RestFull API Crowdfunding using gin and gorm (golang);
- Implement payment gateway Midtrans.
- Create Application Database using RDS.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITAS HANDAYANI MAKASSAR TEKNIK INFORMATIKA

October, 2018 - August, 2023

- Graduated with High Honors;
- Cumulative GPA 3,59

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION
Course April, 2021 | DICODING

Pemrograman Web

- Learn HTML;
- Learn CSS;
- Learn Javascript;
- · Learn Node JS;
- Learn AWS

Licenses and Certificates Pemrograman Web by Dicoding (Link)

April, 2021

Pemrograman Javascript by Dicoding(Link)

July, 2022

Pemrograman BackEnd by Dicoding(Link)

September, 2023

Language Indonesia (Proficient)

English (Intermediate)